this
exercise requires us to write two
methods
so that the test cases we've been given
will output true
so looking at the test cases we can see
that we have an
add method and a multiply method
so we know those are the two methods we
need to write
and we can see that each of these
methods accepts two arguments
i'm going to comment out line three
where we have a test case for our
multiply method and just begin
working with our add method for now
we can see that the arguments passed to
our add method will be
integers so we'll name our parameters
num1 and num2
again looking at the test cases on lines
5 and 6
we can see that the return value of our
add method
should just be the sum of our two
arguments
and in order to return the sum we just
need to perform that addition
on the last line executed in the method
in this case we'll just have one line in
our method
where we add num1 and num2 so now we can
run our code
and see if these test cases are
outputting true
and they are now we can go back
and take a look at defining the multiply
method
i'm going to uncomment the test case for
our multiply method
and we'll take a closer look at the
arguments passed to this method
we have method calls to the add method
passed in as arguments to the multiply
method
this may seem confusing but what this
does
is passes the return value of invoking
this add method as an
argument to multiply so as our first
argument passed to the multiply method
we're invoking the add method
and passing the integers 2 and 2
as arguments as we can see above
on line 9 in our test case for the add
method
this will return 4. the second argument
we passed
to the multiply method is again a call
to the add method
however this time we're passing in
arguments five and four
and as seen on line ten this will return
the integer nine
so when we invoke the multiply method
it will use the integer 4 and the
integer 9
as its arguments
so again we'll call these two integers
num1
and num2 on line six
we'll multiply num1 by num2 and that
product will be returned from the method
i'm going to run the code again now with
the test case for our multiply method
and see that that will output true as
well
and it does
so we're successfully returning true for
all of the test cases
and our code is functioning
appropriately